{
    "subject": "resource/Born_in_East_L.A._(song)",
    "predicate": "property/artist",
    "object": "resource/Cheech_&_Chong",
    "human_readable": "The artist of the song 'Born in East L.A.' is Cheech & Chong.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9637753367424011,
            "question": "Are there any other notable songs by Cheech & Chong besides 'Born in East L.A.'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9579429626464844,
            "question": "Who are the artists behind the song 'Born in East L.A.'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.817909300327301,
            "question": "What is the title of the song performed by Cheech & Chong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8037856221199036,
            "question": "Is 'Born in East L.A.' a popular or well-known song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7655187249183655,
            "question": "What genre of music is 'Born in East L.A.' associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7124988436698914,
            "question": "What themes are likely explored in the song 'Born in East L.A.'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6336392760276794,
            "question": "What is Cheech & Chong known for besides music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6202173233032227,
            "question": "When was 'Born in East L.A.' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.52796471118927,
            "question": "What is the overall message conveyed in 'Born in East L.A.'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4346267879009247,
            "question": "Did 'Born in East L.A.' achieve commercial success?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The artist of the song 'Born in East L.A.' is Cheech & Chong.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3660_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall message conveyed in 'Born in East L.A.'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3660_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'Born in East L.A.' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3660_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Cheech & Chong known for besides music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3660_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3660_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3660_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3660_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3660_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3660_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3660_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3660_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3660_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3660_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3660_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The information in the documents supports the triple, so the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThere are multiple mentions of \"Cheech and Chong\" as the creators of the song \"Born in East LA\", which confirms that they are indeed the artists behind the song."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents support that \"Born in East L.A.\" is a song by Cheech & Chong, which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}